{
    "subject": "Y\u016bko_Kobayashi",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Mitsuaki_Hoshino",
    "human_readable": "Y\u016bko Kobayashi is married to Mitsuaki Hoshino.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9565219879150391,
            "question": "To whom is Y\u016bko Kobayashi married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.953056275844574,
            "question": "Is Y\u016bko Kobayashi married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9496477246284485,
            "question": "Who is married to Mitsuaki Hoshino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8885391354560852,
            "question": "What type of relationship exists between Y\u016bko Kobayashi and Mitsuaki Hoshino?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8867982625961304,
            "question": "Based on this information, what can you infer about the relationship between Mitsuaki Hoshino and Y\u016bko Kobayashi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8414758443832397,
            "question": "What is the name of Mitsuaki Hoshino's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7800936102867126,
            "question": "What is the marital status of Y\u016bko Kobayashi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.18341268599033356,
            "question": "Who are the two people involved in a marriage relationship according to this information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.09636310487985611,
            "question": "Can you identify a couple mentioned in this statement?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05932800471782684,
            "question": "Who are you able to connect through their relationship status?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Y\u016bko Kobayashi is married to Mitsuaki Hoshino.",
            "html": "yago_5795_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you identify a couple mentioned in this statement?",
            "html": "yago_5795_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the two people involved in a marriage relationship according to this information?",
            "html": "yago_5795_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the marital status of Y\u016bko Kobayashi?",
            "html": "yago_5795_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_5795_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that Yuko Kobayashi is married to voice actor Mitsuaki Hoshino, and similarly, Mitsuaki Hoshino is mentioned as being married to Y\u016bko Kobayashi (or sometimes spelled as Y\u016bko)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Yuko Kobayashi is married to Mitsuaki Hoshino, which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}